All on my own, I hugged my knees
I couldn’t even see that I was still alive
My wound was filthy and wouldn’t disappear
I kept on caressing it and only hurt it more
Dreams that glowed in gold, soft and peaceful, words witnessed by the wind
Slowly mixing into all the tender feelings in my heart
Through the rainy days, through the sunny days, every single day I loved you
That’s the only thing I can say will always stay the same
But time went on, the promise unfulfilled
My heart protected me, weak as I am,
and gently pushed me on, walking on my own,
while wishing for tomorrow’s days to shine, with a smile
One day, one of these days
I’ll be able to smile
One day, one of these days...
Please allow me the freedom to feel sadness just for now
The end to these days is broken, but I will bring an end to them
Through the rainy days, through the sunny days, every single day you were in my heart
That’s the only thing I can say will always stay the same
And I will go down believing the promise true
With my fragile heart held in two cupped hands
you’ll gently wipe away my overflowing tears
and for your kindness I’ll say to you
“Thank you”