The 20 rules are buried, the 10 commandments crushed, even public facts submerged
In other words: it defies prediction at every turn
Yet calamity doth approach: all over, catastrophes are born screaming, trials strummed by my hand
Are you still going to have that idiotic mentality?
There is not a morsel for you to peck at!
Come now, drown in endless anguish!
Starve to death while clutching at ways to reach the truth!
As the moon crosses the night sky
the waves grow enraged
The cries of seagulls
beckon the turbulent clouds
The golden curse
the words left behind
and the secretive smile
all become smeared with crimson
What are you looking for, with your eyes sealed shut?
Try as you may to collect the shattered fragments
they shall spill from the hands that touch them
and never reach you
The tapestry of truth and lies
Without love, it cannot be ‘seen’
Without love, without love, you won’t see the truth